PROFILE

Strong background in communication, customer relations and support, product and project management, and product design and development. Over seven years of professional experience in major programming languages and operating hardware and software. Strong abilities in project and team leadership. Quick learner with the ability to adapt to the needs our clients and business. Highly efficient with a focus on delivering at the greatest quality.

EXPERIENCE

SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER/TECH ARCHITECT, SURVEYMONKEY, LLC.; PALO ALTO, CA - FEBRUARY 2010-PRESENT

- Technical Lead across Survey Monkey's stack including multiple projects, most recently our new "Enterprise" feature.
- Responsible for quality of products which included: code reviews, design and architecture of front-end code base, models/views of underlying system, design patterns and standards for front-end development
- Implement, maintain, and improve user-experience on surveymonkey.com through optimization of code base both front and back-end.
- · Designed and implemented the infrastructure for test and production systems
- Designed, and maintained base library system into the extensible system maintained by over 100 engineers today.

SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER, YAHOO INC.; SUNNYVALE, CA — MARCH 2008-FEBRUARY 2010

- Development Lead Responsible for quality of products which included: code reviews, design and architecture reviews and standards, and task assignment for high-performance, extensible, and scalable platform
- Designer and architect of "widgets" for our platform's for extensibility, scalability, ease of use, and reusability for high-performance webpages
- Feature Prioritization and Cost/Benefit Analysis
- · Standardized development practices and processes of software for quick-turnaround and ease-of-use

SOLUTIONS ENGINEER, YAHOO INC.; SUNNYVALE, CA — AUGUST 2007-MARCH 2008

- Designed, prototyped, and implemented solutions for advertisers and internal teams to drive revenue "upstream"
- · Liaison for client relations and requirements
- · Rapid Application Development to provide quick turnaround times for all end to end processes
- · Maintaining client relationships for future projects and project updates
- As Senior member, responsible for knowledge transfer and training of other members in the group when needed
- Built and improved feed based system to drive revenue through existing advertising programs and help influence new initiatives.
- Drove projects to improve workflow of Business to Business transactions and Consumer to Business transaction to improve revenue impact

EDUCATION

University of California Santa Cruz — B.S., Information & Technology Management, 2006. GPA: 3.74 - Highest Honors in Major, College Honors